Guide to the Cannon Mills Records, 1836-1983 RL.00187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Executive Office Files Series, 1923-1980, bulk 1940s-1970s
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - Retirement Plan:
      - Audits of Accounts of the Trust Fund for the Retirement Income Plan for Cannon Mills Co., Its Subsidiaries, and Associated Companies, 1948-1964 (16 vols.) (Box 75)
    - Retirement Plan: (Box 76)
      - Pension Plan Proposed by C. P. Dawson Co., Pension Planning, New York City, 1943 (Box 76)
      - Pension Plans at Other Companies, 1945-1951 and undated, 4 folders (Box 76)
      - Preliminary Reports on Employee Benefit Plans by Johnson and Higgins, New York, 1947 (Box 76)
      - Trust Agreement, 1947 (Box 76)
      - Valuation Reports on Retirement Plan by Johnson and Higgins, 1947-1948 (Box 76)
      - Valuation Reports on Retirement Plan by Johnson and Higgins, 1949-1950 (Box 76)
    - Retirement Plan: (Box 77)
      - Valuation Reports on Retirement Plan by Johnson and Higgins, 1951-1963, 7 folders (Box 77)
    - Rocky River Regional Water Utility System Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 77)
    - Sales and Production Reports, 1931-1945 (Box 77)
    - Sheet and Pillow Case Price Lists, 1933 (Box 77)
    - Sheet Sample Booklets, 1927 (Folder 1) (Box 77)
    - Sheet Sample Booklets, 1927 (Folder 2) (Box 78)
    - Sheeting and Miscellaneous Orders Shipped, 1927-1930, A-W, 5 folders (Box 78)
    - Social Circle Cotton Mill Tender Offer, 1978 (Box 78)
    - South Cicero Terminal, Cicero, Illinois, Bemis Lester (Box 78)
    - Architect, Kannapolis, N.C.:
      - Architectural Drawings for Shop Building and Scale House, 1952 (Box 78)
      - Paving and Fencing, 1951-1953 (Box 78)
      - Photographs (Box 78)
    - Suits in Courts: (Box 79)
      - 1972-1979, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Daisy Crawford (Retaliation for Protesting Against Racial Discrimination), 1969-1976 (Box 79)
    - Superintendent:
      - Spinners' and Carders' Daily Reports, 1933, Aug.-Sept. (Box 79)
    - Tender Offer Bill, North Carolina General Assembly, 1977 (Box 79)
    - Tribune Interview, 1972, April 12 (Changes That Have Taken Place in Textiles in Last Few Years) (Box 79)
    - Unions: (Box 80)
      - Build Independent Unions under New Deal Legislation, 1942 (Box 80)
      - Letters from Concerned Persons Concerning Union Vote, 1974-1975 (bulk, 1974), 2 folders (Box 80)
      - Letters from Employees Concerning Union Vote, 1974, 2 folders (Box 80)
        Scope and Contents
        Audio letter on audiocassette (RL00187-CS-0001) digitized and removed to Box AV001.
        - Audio letter on audio cassette. (Box AV-001, Audio-cassette RL00187-CS-0001, Digital-materials RL00187-SET-0001)
      - Letters Written to Cannon People, 1976 (Box 80)
      - Letters Written to Employees Concerning Union, 1974 (Box 80)
      - National Labor Relations Board, 1974-1975 (Box 80)
    - Suit:
      - Textile Workers Union of America and Pauline Freeman, 1974 (Box 80)
      - Textile Workers Union of America, 1975-1976 (Box 80)
      - Textile Workers Union of America: Cartoons Against (Box 80)
    - Unions: (Box 81)
      - Textile Workers Union of America Suit, 1974 (Box 81)
      - Union Matters, 1974-1976 (Box 81)
    - W. T. Grant Company, 1975-1977, 3 folders
      - 1978, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - W. T. Grant Company, 1979 (Box 82)
    - Wage and Tax Tables, 1951, Nov. 1 (Box 82)
    - Wiscassett Mills:
      - LIFO Inventories and Taxes, 1975 (Box 82)
    - Wool Top, 1951-1952 (Box 82)
- Executive Office Files: 1950Series
  Chiefly correspondence and files for organizations that dealt with state and national issues of interest to business. National Cotton Council of American material includes correspondence, memoranda, and kits containing speeches for use on radio and elsewhere about national agricultural, economic, labor, and medical issues. Officials represented in this series include Charles A. Cannon, president; Hearne Swink, secretary and vice president; G. A. Batte, Jr., secretary to Mr. Cannon; Joe C. Ridenhour; and T. C. Haywood. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files
    - Invoices, Cannon Mills, Inc., New York (Box 82)
    - M Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 82)
    - N Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 82)
    - National Cotton Council of America: (Box 83)
      - Correspondence (Box 83)
      - Memoranda (Box 83)
      - Printed Material, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - National Cotton Council of America Kits:
      - Brannon Plan (Box 83)
      - Deficit Financing (Box 83)
      - Fair Employment Practices Commission (Box 83)
      - Socialized Medicine (Box 83)
      - Taft-Hartley Act (Box 83)
    - Newspaper Clipping, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - North Carolina (State of) (Box 84)
    - North Carolina Cotton Manufacturers' Association (Box 84)
    - North Carolina Fair Tax Association (Box 84)
    - North Carolina Industrial Council (Box 84)
    - North Carolina Traffic League (Box 84)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 84)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 84)
    - Penney, J.C., Co. (Box 84)
    - Q Miscellaneous (Box 84)
    - R Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Requests for Employment, etc., 2 folders (Box 85)
    - S Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - S Miscellaneous (Folder 3) (Box 86)
    - Saco-Lowell Shops (Box 86)
    - Social Circle Cotton Mills (Box 86)
    - Southern Sheet and Supply Company (Box 86)
    - Standard and Poor's Corporation (Box 86)
- Executive Office Files: 1952 Series
  These files are considerably more complete than those in the series for 1950. Larger files include: miscellaneous correspondence; several mills in the Cannon group, especially Central and Wiscassett; state and national industry organizations; Ewing-Thomas Corp. of Chester, Pa., and the U.S. government (New York Quartermaster Procurement Agency). many important writers and topics appear in the extensive miscellaneous correspondence files. Cannon, Swink, Ridenhour, Batte, and Haywood continue to be principals in the correspondence. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files
    - C Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 86)
    - Central Mills, Central, S.C.: Jan.-Dec. (Box 86)
    - Central Mills, Central, S.C.: (Box 87)
      - Bank Balances, Jan.-Dec. (Box 87)
      - Weekly Reports, Jan.-Sept. (Box 87)
    - Churches:
      - Company Transactions (Box 87)
    - Columbus Coated Fabrics, Columbus, Ohio: Jan.-Dec. (Box 87)
    - Cotton Manufacturers Association of Georgia, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - D Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Duke Power Company: (Box 88)
      - Demand Readings, 3 folders (Box 88)
    - E Miscellaneous (Box 88)
    - Ewing-Thomas Corp., Chester, Pa.:
      - Contracts (Box 88)
      - Correspondence (Box 88)
      - Purchase Orders (Box 88)
      - Reports, Price Lists, etc. (Box 88)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 89)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 89)
    - H Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - I Miscellaneous (Box 89)
    - Imperial Cotton Mills (Box 89)
    - J Miscellaneous (Box 89)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 89)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 89)
    - M Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 90)
    - Mill-Power Supply Co. Club, Marion, N.C.:
      - (Duke Family and Lake James) (Box 90)
    - Montgomery Ward (Box 90)
    - Moody's Investors Service (Box 90)
    - N Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 90)
    - National Cotton Council of America:
      - Correspondence (Box 90)
    - National Cotton Council of America: (Box 91)
      - Reports and Publications (Box 91)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 3 folders (Box 91)
    - North Carolina (State of) (Box 91)
    - North Carolina Cotton Manufacturers' Association (Box 91)
    - North Carolina Traffic League (Box 91)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 92)
    - Penney, J. C., Co. (Box 92)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 92)
    - Q Miscellaneous (Box 92)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 92)
    - Requests from Employees (Box 92)
    - S Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 92)
    - S Miscellaneous: (Box 93)
      - Sept.-Dec. (Box 93)
    - Social Circle Cotton Mills (Box 93)
    - South Carolina Textile Manufacturers' Association (Box 93)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 93)
    - Traffic Department Representing American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, etc. (Box 93)
    - U Miscellaneous (Box 93)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce (Box 93)
    - United States Department of Commerce (Box 93)
    - United States Government Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Box 93)
    - United States Government Miscellaneous, July-Dec. (Box 94)
    - United States Government Procurement:
      - New York Quartermaster Procurement Agency:
        - Invoices, 5.5 oz Oxford (Box 94)
        - Invoices, 6.5 Oxford (Box 94)
        - Invoices, 5 oz. poplin (Box 94)
        - Invoices, 9 oz. sateen (Box 94)
    - United States Government Procurement:
      - Yarn File (Buying of Yarn for Contracts) (Box 94)
    - United States Government Reports on Sheeting, Oxford, Sateen, etc. (Box 94)
    - United States Navy Department (Box 94)
    - United States Quartermaster Department: (Box 95)
      - Jan.-Dec., 3 folders (Box 95)
      - V Miscellaneous (Box 95)
      - W. Miscellaneous (Box 95)
      - W. T. Grant Co. (Box 95)
    - Wiscassett Mills:
      - General (Box 95)
    - Wiscassett Mills: (Box 96)
      - Production Reports (Box 96)
      - Stock (Box 96)
      - Weekly Cash and Stock Reports (Box 96)
      - Yarn File (Box 96)
    - Y Miscellaneous (Box 96)
    - Young Men's Christian Association: Local (Box 96)
- Executive Office Files: 1970 Series
  Primarily files for officials, departments, and plants within the company, including extensive sales reports from several regions in the country. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files
    - Batte, George A., Jr.: (Box 96)
      - Correspondence, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Cannon, Charles Albert:
      - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb. (Box 96)
    - Charles Albert Cannon: (Box 97)
      - Correspondence, March-Dec., 9 folders (Box 97)
    - Cannon, J. Harris: (Box 98)
      - Correspondence, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Cannon Mills Miscellaneous:
      - Jan.-Dec., 4 folders (Box 98)
    - Commercial Warehouse, Paterson, N.J., June-Nov. (Box 98)
    - Connor, Claude (Southwest Region Sales and Quota Performance) (Box 98)
    - Cotton Department, 1960-1969, 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Cotton Department, 1969-1970, 4 folders (Box 99)
    - Dallas Warehouse (Box 99)
    - Gold, Comann D. (Southern Region Sales Quotas) (Box 99)
    - Grey Goods Department Reports, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 99)
    - Hardoon, Daphne E. (Box 100)
    - Holt, Don S.:
      - Correspondence, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 100)
    - Hornaday, Harold (Vice President) (Box 100)
    - Jenkins, Louis W. (Vice President) (Box 100)
    - Jolly, James R. (New York Office) (Box 100)
    - Labas, Sara (New York Office) (Box 100)
    - Levering, H. Brune (New York Office) (Box 100)
    - MacLaughlin, W. F. (Sales Quota Analyses) (Box 100)
    - Mann, W. H. (Including Sales and Sales Quota Reports) (Box 100)
    - Phases (?) for Each Month (Box 100)
    - Central Region Sales Quotas (Box 100)
    - Miller, S. F. (Assistant Treasurer and Assistant Secretary) (Box 101)
    - Pellman, Anne (Publicity Clippings) (Box 101)
    - Personnel Department (Box 101)
    - Plant 2 (Box 101)
    - Plant 3 (Box 101)
    - Plant 5 (Box 101)
    - Plant 6:
      - 1961, March- 1970, Dec., 2 folders (Box 101)
      - Summary of Bedspreads (Box 101)
    - Plant 8 (Box 101)
    - Plant 10 (Box 101)
    - Plant 12 (Box 101)
    - Plant 14 (Box 101)
    - Plant 16 (Box 101)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 101)
    - Purchasing Department Monthly Reports (Box 101)
    - Quinn, W. L. (Towel Loom Scheduling, etc.) (Box 101)
    - Recommendations for Buildings and Equipment (Box 102)
    - Ridenhour, Joe C. (Vice President) (Box 102)
    - Safety Department: 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Saunders, J. W. (Eastern Region Sales Quotas) (Box 102)
    - Spence, Elmer L. (Vice President) (Box 102)
    - Swiggett, R. C. (Central Region Sales Reports) (Box 102)
    - Swink, Hearne (Box 102)
    - Toumey, Hugh J. (Sales) (Box 102)
    - Traffic Department (Box 102)
    - Wilson, F. L. (Plant Running Schedules, etc.; Director of Manufacturing) (Box 102)
- Executive Office Files: 1971 Series
  Primarily files A-M including correspondence with officials, sales data, business with textile mills and related companies, and national and state industry organizations. Officials represented include President Cannon and Vice Presidents Batte, J. H. Cannon, and Harold P. Hornaday. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - A Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec., 3 folders (Box 103)
    - Amazon Cotton Mills, Thomasville, N.C.:
      - Jan.-Dec. (Box 103)
      - Bank Balances (Box 103)
      - Synthetic Fiber Reports (Box 103)
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute:
      - Bulletins (Box 103)
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute: (Box 104)
      - Correspondence (Box 104)
      - Form Letters (Box 104)
      - Market Division (Box 104)
      - Miscellaneous Data (Box 104)
      - Public Relations Pointers (Box 104)
    - America's Textile Reporter (Box 104)
    - Applications for Employment (Box 104)
    - B Miscellaneous:
      - Jan.-Aug. (Box 104)
    - B Miscellaneous, Sept.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Bankers Trust Company, New York City (Box 105)
    - Barringer, L. T., and Company, Cotton, Memphis, Tenn. (Box 105)
    - Batte, George A., Jr.:
      - Correspondence, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 105)
    - C Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec., 5 folders (Box 106)
    - Cabarrus Bank and Trust Company (Box 106)
    - Cannon, Charles Albert: (Box 107)
      - Correspondence, January-April, 4 folders (Box 107)
    - Cannon, J. Harris:
      - Correspondence, Jan.-Dec., 3 folders (Box 107)
    - Cannon Homemaking Service and Consumer Service:
      - Correspondence, Jan.-March (Box 107)
    - Cannon Homemaking Service and Consumer Service, April-Dec., 3 folders (Box 108)
    - Cannon Mills Miscellaneous (Box 108)
    - Castle, Thomas H. (Advertising, New York Office) (Box 108)
    - Churches (Box 108)
    - Cincinnati Warehouse (Box 108)
    - Columbus Coated Fabrics (Box 109)
    - Commercial Warehouse (Box 109)
    - Concord Chamber of Commerce (Box 109)
    - Connor, Claude (Southwest Region Sales Quotas) (Box 109)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 109)
    - Dallas Warehouse (Box 109)
    - Du Pont de Nemours and Co. (Box 109)
    - Duke Power Company (Box 109)
    - E Miscellaneous (Box 109)
    - Ervin, Senator Sam J. (Box 109)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 109)
    - First National City Bank of New York (Box 110)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 110)
    - Georgia Textile Manufacturers Association (Box 110)
    - Gold, Comann D. (Southern Region Sales Quotas) (Box 110)
    - H Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 110)
    - Haedka, C., and Co., New York City (Box 111)
    - Harris, Upham and Co. (Securities and Commodities) (Box 111)
    - Hentz, H., and Co. (Securities and Commodities, New York City) (Box 111)
    - Holt, Don S., Jan.-Dec., 3 folders (Box 111)
    - Hornaday, Harold P. (Vice President): Correspondence, Nov.-Dec. (Box 111)
    - I Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 111)
    - Imperial Cotton Mills and Social Circle Cotton Mills:
      - Bank Balances (Box 111)
    - Jolly, James R. (New York Office) (Box 111)
    - Labas, Sara (Fashion Merchandising Coordinator) (Box 111)
    - Levering, H. Brune (Bedspread Bulletin) (Box 111)
    - MacLaughlin, W. F. (Sales Quota Analysis) (Box 112)
    - Mann, W. H. (Sales Quotas) (Box 112)
    - Meehan, E. P. (Mid-Central Region Sales Quotas) (Box 112)
    - Royal Robes, Inc., 1969, 1971 (Box 112)
    - Saunders, J. W. (Eastern Region Sales Quotas) (Box 112)
    - South Carolina Textile Manufacturers Association (Box 112)
    - Swiggett, R. C. (Central Regional Sales Reports) (Box 112)
    - Toumey, H. J. (New York Office) (Box 112)
- Executive Office Files, 1979, Series
  Includes files A-C and L-Z that are somewhat more extensive than the records for 1950, 1952, 1970, and 1971. Concerns various aspects of production and sales, Wiscassett Mills, dealings with state and national industry and governmental organizations, especially the American Textile Manufacturers Institute and the North Carolina Textile Manufacturers Association. Numerous officials are represented in the correspondence including President and Chairman Hornaday, Vice Chairman and Treasurer Batte, Vice Presidents Adams, Jenkins, and Spence, Secretary Beck, Don S. Holt, Joe C. Ridenhour, and others. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - A-A1 Miscellaneous (Box 113)
    - AM Miscellaneous (Box 113)
    - An-Az Miscellaneous (Including advertising report from N. W. Ayer) (Box 113)
    - Adams, Andrew W. (Executive Vice President) (Box 113)
    - Advertising (Box 113)
    - Amazon Cotton Mills (Box 113)
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute:
      - Background Materials, Area Meetings (Box 113)
      - Board of Directors' Meetings, Feb. and April (Box 113)
      - Board of Directors' Meeting, Nov. (Box 113)
      - Budget, Finance, and Policy Committee (Box 113)
      - Bulletins (Box 113)
      - Correspondence, Jan.-March (Box 113)
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute: (Box 114)
      - Correspondence, April-Dec., 5 folders (Box 114)
      - Directory (Box 114)
      - Energy Policy Committee (Box 114)
      - Market Division (Box 114)
      - Public Relations Pointers (Box 114)
      - Safety and Health Committee (Box 114)
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute: (Box 115)
      - Textile Hi-Lights (Box 115)
      - Textile Trends (Box 115)
    - Argo, Ken R. (Box 115)
    - B-Be Miscellaneous (Box 115)
    - Bi-Bo Miscellaneous (Box 115)
    - Br-Bu Miscellaneous (Box 115)
    - Babson, David L., and Co., Investment Counsel (Box 115)
    - Bank Balances (Box 115)
    - Bankers Trust Company (Box 115)
    - Barringer, L. T., and Co., Cotton, Memphis, Tenn., Jan.- Dec., 3 folders (Box 116)
    - Bedspread Sales for Five Years, Jan.-Dec., 4 folders (Box 116)
    - Billings and Projections: (Box 117)
      - Jan.-Dec. (Box 117)
      - Spreadsheets (Box 117)
    - C-Ce Miscellaneous (Box 117)
    - Ch-Cl Miscellaneous (Box 117)
    - Co-Cu Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 117)
    - Cabarrus Bank and Trust Co. (Box 117)
    - Cannon Mills Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 117)
    - Cannon News (Box 118)
    - Celanese Fibers Marketing Company (Box 118)
    - Chemical Laboratory (Box 118)
    - Clemson University (Box 118)
    - Comparative Cost Statements (Box 118)
    - Concord Chamber of Commerce (Box 118)
    - Conference Board, New York (Box 118)
    - Consolidated Poundage Reports:
      - Jan.-June (Box 118)
      - July-Dec. and Jan. 3, 1980 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence:
      - Adams, Andrew W. (Executive Vice President) (Box 118)
      - Argo, Ken R., Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Correspondence: (Box 119)
      - Batte, George A. (Treasurer and Vice Chairman) (Box 119)
      - Beck, Billy T. (Secretary) (Box 119)
      - Hornaday, Harold P. (President and Chairman) (Box 119)
      - Jones, Branson (Box 119)
      - Patterson, John (Box 119)
    - Cotton, Inc. (Box 119)
    - Cotton Department (Box 119)
    - Fiberfill (Box 119)
    - Grey Goods Department (Box 119)
    - Holt, Don S. (Box 119)
    - Inventories (Box 119)
    - Jenkins, L. W. (Vice President) (Box 119)
    - Jones, Branson (Box 119)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 119)
    - Loom Hours Operated, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Loom Production Reports (Box 119)
    - Mc Miscellaneous (Box 120)
    - M-Me Miscellaneous (Box 120)
    - Mi-Mz Miscellaneous (Box 120)
    - Maiden Knitting Mills, Maiden, N.C.:
      - Jan.-Dec. (Box 120)
      - Cash Reports (Box 120)
    - Medical Department (Box 120)
    - Mill Bookings (Sales Summaries) (Box 120)
    - Mississippi Agricultural and Industrial Board (Box 120)
    - Na Miscellaneous (Box 120)
    - Ne-Nu Miscellaneous (Box 121)
    - National Cotton Council (Box 121)
    - National Knitwear Manufacturing Association (Box 121)
    - National Right to Work Committee (Box 121)
    - Newman, H. H., III (Box 121)
    - Newspaper Articles (Box 121)
    - North Carolina (State) (Box 121)
    - North Carolina Citizens Association (Box 121)
    - North Carolina Textile Manufacturers Association:
      - Jan.-April (Box 121)
    - North Carolina Textile Manufacturers Association, May- Dec., 4 folders (Box 122)
    - North Carolina Universities (Box 122)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 122)
    - Order and Data Processing Department (Box 122)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 122)
    - Patterson, John (Box 123)
    - Penney, J. C., Company (Box 123)
    - Personnel Department (Box 123)
    - Plant Locations (Box 123)
    - Plant No. 6, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders
      - Decorative Fabric and Yarn Report (Box 123)
    - Plants 3-5, 7-12, 14, 16-19 (Box 123)
    - Pritchard, Carlton S., Jr., Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Public Relations Department (Box 123)
    - Purchase Orders (Box 123)
    - Purchasing Department:
      - April-May (Box 123)
      - Monthly Reports, Jan.-May (Box 123)
      - Monthly Reports, June-Dec. (Box 123)
    - Q Miscellaneous (Box 123)
    - Quinn, W. L. (Box 123)
    - Ra-Re Miscellaneous (Box 124)
    - Rh-Ry Miscellaneous (Box 124)
    - Returns and Allowances (Box 124)
    - Ridenhour, Joe C. (Box 124)
    - S-Sc Miscellaneous (Box 124)
    - Sc-Si Miscellaneous (Box 124)
    - Sk-Sp Miscellaneous (Box 124)
    - St-Sy Miscellaneous (Box 124)
    - Safety Department, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Sheet Sales, Jan.-Dec., 3 folders (Box 125)
    - Social Circle Cotton Mill (Box 125)
    - South Carolina Textile Manufacturers Association, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Spence, E. L. (Senior Vice President), Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Spindle Hours Operated, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Spindle Hours Operated Outside Plants, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Stock Quotations, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Summary of Sales Department, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 126)
    - T Miscellaneous, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Tabulating Reports (Box 127)
    - Terry and Huck Production Reports (Box 127)
    - Towel Production (Box 127)
    - Towel Sales for Five Years, Feb.-Dec., 3 folders (Box 127)
    - Traffic Department (Box 127)
    - Training Department (Box 127)
    - U Miscellaneous (Box 128)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce (Box 128)
    - U.S. Government, Jan.-Dec., 3 folders (Box 128)
    - U.S. News and World Report: Subscriptions (Box 128)
    - United Way (Box 128)
    - V Miscellaneous (Box 128)
    - W Miscellaneous (Box 129)
    - Wachovia Bank and Trust Company (Box 129)
    - Weekly Order Reports (Box 129)
    - Weekly Report of Employees Needed, Employed, and Terminated (Box 129)
    - Whaley-Eaton Service's American Letter: Sample with Routing Slip (Box 129)
    - Wiscassett Mills, Jan.-Dec., 3 folders
      - Bank Balances (Box 129)
      - Billings Reports (Box 129)
      - Cotton Consumed (Box 129)
      - Cotton Position (Box 129)
      - Daily Yarn Reports (Box 129)
    - Wiscassett Mills: (Box 130)
      - Dyed Yarn Shipments (Box 130)
      - Pinsonic Log Summaries (Box 130)
      - Pinsonic Production and Shipments (Box 130)
      - Purchases of Fiberfill (Box 130)
      - Roll Stock Inventories (Box 130)
      - Weekly Operating Reports (Box 130)
    - XYZ Miscellaneous (Box 130)
    - YMCA (Box 130)
- Harold P. Hornaday Series, 1971-1982
  Chiefly minutes of the Board of Directors' Audit Committee and Hornaday's expense reports and speeches. During this period he served as vice president, president, and chairman of the Board of Directors. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - Information Folder (Box 130)
    - Board of Directors:
      - Audit Committee Minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 130)